http://www.inkpal.com/pages/privacy-policy

Skip to content
Inkpal Security and Privacy Policy
Inkpal Secure Shopping Guarantee:
Click Here to Find Out ABOUT SSL CERTIFICATES
Security is a primary concern for us at Inkpal.com. To ensure safe shopping, we use 256-bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption security, the highest level of security available today for secure e-commerce transactions. All pages containing account information are thoroughly encrypted while in transit, ensuring that your information will not be compromised even in the case of third-party attacks.
SSL encryption makes online shopping perhaps the safest way to use your credit card. After setting up an account with us, your credit card information will NOT be stored on our server.
Inkpal Privacy Policy
At Inkpal.com, we know that many internet users are concerned about the safety of their personal information while shopping online. Backed by the largest trust authorities on the web, we do all we can to make sure the transferring of your information remains secure. We respect and value our customers and their privacy.
All account information is used for order processing and account maintenance purposes only. While shipping addresses are passed on to our suppliers only when one of our outsourcing partners is needed to fulfill an order, billing addresses and credit card information will never be forwarded. Please contact us immediately at contactus@inkpal.com if you suspect that your private information has been misused.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to and collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do so at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on this website.
Security
We take every precaution to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via this website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever, we collect sensitive information, such as credit card data, that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. We also use the latest SSL (provider of 256 bit encryption) to help ensure the safety of your information. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information.
Updates
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page. If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via Contact Us Page.
Orders
We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you.
About Sharing Information
Information gathered by Inkpal is never shared, sold or rented to a third party except to fill the orders you have made with us.
Links Found on Inkpal.com
This web site may contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Added to your cart:
(-)
Cart subtotal
Net Orders Checkout
Item
Price
Qty
Total
Subtotal
$0.00
Mozambique
Myanmar (Burma)
Namibia
Nauru
Nepal
Netherlands
Netherlands Antilles
New Caledonia
New Zealand
Nicaragua
Zimbabwe
AlabamaAlaskaAmerican SamoaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFederated States of MicronesiaFloridaGeorgiaGuamHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarshall IslandsMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaNorthern Mariana IslandsOhioOklahomaOregonPalauPennsylvaniaPuerto RicoRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirgin IslandsVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingArmed Forces AmericasArmed Forces EuropeArmed Forces Pacific
Shipping Methods
